{
    "questions": 
    [
        {
            "question": "Sweden",
            "answers": ["se", "no", "dk", "fi"],
            "correct": "se"
        },
        {
            "question": "Bulgaria",
            "answers": ["pl", "hu", "it", "bg"],
            "correct": "bg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Estonia",
            "answers": ["fi", "ee", "lu", "gr"],
            "correct": "ee"
        },
        {
            "question": "Azerbaijan",
            "answers": ["az", "tr", "lb", "tn"],
            "correct": "az"
        },
        {
            "question": "Kenya",
            "answers": ["ht", "mm", "ke", "mu"],
            "correct": "ke"
        },
        {
            "question": "Argentina",
            "answers": ["ar", "uy", "ve", "br"],
            "correct": "ar"
        },
        {
            "question": "Nicaragua",
            "answers": ["mx", "pr", "ve", "ni"],
            "correct": "ni"
        },
        {
            "question": "Vietnam",
            "answers": ["vn", "tw", "af", "tl"],
            "correct": "vn"
        },
        {
            "question": "Peru",
            "answers": ["bo", "cl", "pr", "ve"],
            "correct": "pr"
        },
        {
            "question": "Congo",
            "answers": ["cg", "cf", "cm", "ao"],
            "correct": "cg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Bosnia and Herzegovina",
            "answers": ["cx", "ba", "gm", "kosovo"],
            "correct": "ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "Japan",
            "answers": ["gl", "ne", "mk", "jp"],
            "correct": "jp"
        },
        {
            "question": "Libya",
            "answers": ["mv", "ly", "mr", "pk"],
            "correct": "ly"
        },
        {
            "question": "Somalia",
            "answers": ["so", "sg", "km", "id"],
            "correct": "so"
        },
        {
            "question": "Croatia",
            "answers": ["ba", "si", "mk", "hr"],
            "correct": "hr"
        },
        {
            "question": "Serbia",
            "answers": ["rs", "ad", "ru", "py"],
            "correct": "rs"
        },
        {
            "question": "Ukraine",
            "answers": ["rs", "td", "ua", "ro"],
            "correct": "ua"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mauritania",
            "answers": ["ae", "mr", "az", "cc"],
            "correct": "mr"
        },
        {
            "question": "Ghana",
            "answers": ["gh", "jm", "az", "ma"],
            "correct": "gh"
        },
        {
            "question": "Lichtenstein",
            "answers": ["lu", "it", "pe", "li"],
            "correct": "li"
        },
        {
            "question": "Austria",
            "answers": ["lv", "hu", "at", "pe"],
            "correct": "at"
        },
        {
            "question": "Indonesia",
            "answers": ["pl", "pe", "mc", "id"],
            "correct": "id"
        }
    ]
}